<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NBA Analyzer</string>
    <string name="nav_item_my_team">My Team</string>
    <string name="nav_item_teams">Teams</string>
    <string name="nav_item_help">Help</string>
    <string name="tab_team_preview">Team Preview</string>
    <string name="tab_boxscore">Boxscore</string>
    <string name="tab_western">Western Conference</string>
    <string name="tab_eastern">Eastern Conference</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="team_logo">Team Logo</string>
    <string name="chart1_paragraph">
        Advanced statistics are displayed on the radar chart that allow
        evaluating the performance of a team during matches. The statistics included are the
        offensive and defensive rating, the percentage of defensive and offensive rebounds percentage
        and the percentage of efficient field goals. With these data we can get a fairly accurate
        preliminary idea about the offensive and defensive capabilities of the team.
    </string>
    <string name="chart2_paragraph">
        This bar chart shows the starter lineup usage.  This statistic
        indicates the percentage of offensive plays the player finishes. This graph is intended to
        offer a vision of which player has the most weight in the team\'s attack. This allows the
        defense to focus on the player with the most offensive volume, focusing the opponent\'s
        study on that player.
    </string>
    <string name="chart3_paragraph">
        This stacked bar graph shows the team score distributed by player positions.
        Within each position the points scored are divided into starters and substitutes.
        This information allows identifying the most important positions within the starting
        and alternate quintets.
    </string>
    <string name="chart4_paragraph">
        This pie chart includes for each position the percentage of the points scored
        by the team. In this graph it is observed which position is the highest scorer in each team
        and on which one has to have a greater defensive presence.
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p1">
        To find the different styles of play within the classic basketball positions, a machine
        learning model has been used that is capable of finding relationships between players based
        on their advanced statistics. For each position a subdivision has been made, in each division
        there is a more important statistic that defines the style of play of those players.
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p2">
        The point guard position has been divided into 5 sets. For each one a label is provided to
        identify the style of play. \n
        In cluster 0, starting point guards have been grouped whose offensive rating is high, as well
        as the percentage of assists they distribute. This is why it has been labeled as: \"Scorer Playmaker\". \n
        In cluster 1 the most important statistic seems to be the offensive rating, although it is not
        very high, and we can usually find second-level players. The assigned label is: \"Secondary
        Scorer\". \n
        In cluster 2 the most important statistic seems to be the percentage of attendances,
        which reaches almost fifty percent. The label assigned to these players is: \"Playmaker\". \n
        In cluster 3, the combination of the offensive rating and the floor percentage stand out,
        which are quite high. The players grouped here are effective scorers and the tag that has
        been assigned is: \"Accurate Scorer\". \n
        For the 4 cluster we have defensive experts, players who are capable of defending the best
        points guards in the league. Their label is: \"Defender\". \n
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p3">
        To cluster the shooting guards, 6 different groups have been necessary to try to explain the
        different types of shooting guards. \n
        In cluster 0 the shooting guards that are capable of performing on the defensive and offensive
        side have been grouped, especially standing out in the three-point shot. Its label is: \"3 and D\". \n
        In cluster 1 there are shooting guards with high scoring ability, this is their main skill.
        The way they tend to score the majority of their points is by shooting three or medium
        distance shots. The label assigned to it is: \"Secondary Shooter\". \n
        In cluster 2 we find players with a low offensive rating despite having a high use. This
        indicates that they are players with a high volume of shots within their teams, but with
        poor percentages. The assigned label is: \"Inefficient Scorer\". \n
        In cluster 3 we find shooting guards who, despite having a not very high offensive rating,
        have high success rates. This may be indicative that your majority of points are scored near
        the rim. The label assigned to it is: \"Efficient Scorer\". \n
        In cluster 4 we find a similar profile to cluster 3. In this case, if we observe the ratio of
        triples it is higher, so we can consider the players in cluster 4 as shooters. Its label is:
        \"Efficient Shooter\". \n
        In cluster 5 the specialized guards in defense have been grouped. Although they are mainly
        defenders, they are able to score with good percentages. The label assigned to them is:
        \"Defender\". \n
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p4">
        For the small forwards 5 groups have been made. In these groups all the forwards in the
        league are classified, so that players with a similar style of play are grouped together. \n
        Cluster 0 includes small forwards that have a low offensive rating but compensate for it with
        a floor percentage and are players with great physical abilities. This indicates that they
        are players who score mostly in the paint. The label assigned to it is: \"Athletic\". \n
        In cluster 1 there are dominant small forwards, the best in their position. They have very
        good offensive and defensive ratings and very high shooting percentages. The label for this
        cluster is: \"2 Side Dominator\". \n
        In cluster 2 they are grouped into small forward who do not stand out in any statistics,
        although the shooting percentages are not bad. These players are labeled as: \"Inefficient
        Scorer\". \n
        In cluster 3 there are players with good scoring abilities, but their use is not very high.
        This indicates that they are players of limited importance on their teams. The label for
        this cluster is: \"Efficient Scorer\". \n
        In cluster 4 small forwards have been grouped with a high offensive rating but a low floor
        percentage. This, added to their high triple ratio, indicates that they are specialists in
        three pointer. The label for this cluster is: \"3 Points Shooter\" \n
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p5">
        Power forwards have also had to be grouped into 6 clusters in order to define the style of
        play of all power forwards in the league. \n
        In cluster 0 there are power forward with good qualities on both sides of the court,
        although they do not become dominators of the game. The label that is assigned to this
        cluster is: \"Two Side\". \n
        In cluster 1 we find power forward with high scoring ability. His offensive rating is not
        strikingly high, but his scoring percentages are. These players are labeled as: \"Primary
        Scorer\". \n
        In Cluster 2 we find power forward with offensive statistics similar to those in Cluster 0,
        although they are slightly worse on defense. The big difference is noticeable in the ratio
        of triples, since they are players with a high ratio and who base part of their scoring on
        three pointers. The label for this cluster is: \"Open 4\". \n
        In cluster 4 they are power forward with very low use. These players have decent offensive
        ratings and good shooting percentages. They are within the rotations of their teams but they
        have little importance within it. The label for this cluster is: \"2 Side Dominator\". \n
        In Cluster 4 they are assisted by energy with very little use. These players have good
        offensive behavior and good shooting percentages. They are within the rotations of their
        teams but they have little importance within it. Theirs tag is: \"Role Player\". \n
        This cluster is similar to the previous one, but the power forwards that comprise it have
        greater usage in their teams, and consequently, greater importance in rotation. The shooting
        percentages are bad, although the offensive rating is low. Theirs tag is: \"Efficient
        Shooter\". \n
    </string>

    <string name="cluster_help_p6">
        The centers have been grouped into 5 clusters that fit the different styles of play. \n
        In cluster 0, centers with little use have been grouped, that is, not many attacks end.
        Despite this, the offensive statistics of these centers are not bad, and they are capable
        of scoring with good percentages. If we look at the defensive rating we can determine that
        they are role players in the team whose main task is to defend. The label for this cluster
        is: \"Role Defender\". \n
        In cluster 1, the centers are important in their equipment, as seen in the average use of
        the cluster. In the offensive part we find that they have a good offensive rating with a
        good floor percentage, this indicates that they are able to score constantly despite not
        having a high number of shots. The actual shooting percentage is quite high, which
        reinforces the idea that they are reliable scorers. The defensive rating is low, so they
        are also good defenders although they do not stand out for it. The label for this cluster
        is: \"Two Way\". \n
        The most dominant pivots have been grouped in cluster 2. As can be seen, their offensive
        rating is very high, although it may be a consequence of the fact that, as observed in the
        real percentage of shots and the percentage of effective field shots, they score the
        majority of their shots. If we also look at their floor percentage, we can identify these
        pivots as attacking finishers, that is, they score the majority of points under the rim.
        On the defensive side they are also capable of dominating, as I know from their defensive
        rating, which is one of the lowest, and the percentage of blocks they make. The label for
        this cluster is: \"2 Side Dominator\". \n
        Cluster 3 has been formed with centers that are capable of opening the court in attack
        and scoring from the three-point line. This is observed in the ratio of 3s attempted,
        despite shooting three, the actual shooting percentage and the percentage of field shooting
        efficiency is relatively high. The use of these pivots is a little higher and this is
        probably due to the fact that more attacks are finished thanks to making a triple from a
        good position. The label for this cluster is: \"Open 5\". \n
        In cluster 4 we find pivots with a lot of weight within the team. Its use is the highest
        among the pivots, which indicates that many of the plays of their teams finish. Neither
        the offensive rating nor the floor percentage are extremely high, but this may be due to
        having a higher shot volume, which consequently causes more shots to miss than the rest.
        The defensive rating does not seem to have had much importance in this cluster, since when
        looking at the values of each player we find very varied data. The actual shooting
        percentage is good and they indicate that they are players who, despite having a high volume
        of shots, are capable of scoring consistently. The label for this cluster is: \"Defender\". \n
    </string>

    <string name="prediction_help_p1">
        Match prediction is done using artificial intelligence methods, specifically a machine
        learning model. This model predicts the winning team based on the advanced statistics of the
        teams involved. In order for the model to be able to make predictions with acceptable
        precision, the model has been trained with the data from the matches played during the
        previous season.
    </string>

    <string name="prediction_help_p2">
        For each match played, the advanced statistics for each team are calculated and the match is
        labeled 1 if the home team wins and 0 otherwise. In total, the information from 633 matches
        has been used to train the model and an accuracy of 75% has been achieved.
    </string>

</resources>
